Previously on Dating Alys Perez.
Would you tell your wife
that I'm not here to be her best friend.
Fier is pregnant.
It's not like I can ask her to leave.
She’s carrying my grandchild.
We both know how
this is going to end.
One of us has to go.
I have a solution, Drake.
I'm leaving.
I haven't a clue as to why
you're tolerating this bullshit!
You're the wife!
Why do you have to leave?
Sometimes I wonder,
why Drake?
Why not just me?
I’m way more handsome, anyway.
- I love you.
Drake?
Oh, right.
When did he ever leave me a note?
I should be used to this.
Hello, Bestie?
Bestie.
Are you at the boutique?
I'll be swinging by.
See you later, bye!
I don't know where Fier went.
Probably at Cristine's.
How'd you know that?
It's the only place she goes.
If she isn't with Drake,
then she must be with Cristine.
Besides, Cristine is the only one who
can put up with her friend’s attitude.
That's harsh.
Why?
It's true.
You know, Bestie,
you really got yourself
into a complicated situation.
I don't know why
you let it get this bad.
What’s your plan?
I'm going to see Fier.
Do you need some backup?
Why? Are you free?
Of course! Just for you.
Why?
There you go.
A message from that creep.
If you ask me, Aya,
we all have our own wars to win.
I can do this on my own.
Face your own battle.
You know, with all of your struggles,
you still find time to annoy me.
Oh, come on, Bestie.
I rarely have fun these days.
Jeez.
Are you sure about that?
I already talked to the twins.
They'll be handling
my papers and everything.
I just need to stay here
until I get my ticket.
You really won't tell me what country?
I'm leaving Drake and everything.
And you being his friend
puts me in jeopardy.
It's better that you don’t know.
But I'm your best friend too.
I know.
We can video chat!
That's not fair.
How can I be the
baby's godmother when
I don't even know
where to send my gifts?
You're such a child sometimes, Cristine.
But you'll see my baby, okay?
We'll video chat as frequent as possible.
And maybe after—
Maybe after some years
when everything's okay,
I'll let you know where we are.
When will you leave?
Leave?
Where is she going?
She's leaving Drake?
Is she really going to deny
Drake his rights as a father?
I don't know yet.
Maybe tonight,
tomorrow or next week?
As soon as possible.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah.
My decision is final.
Hi.
Wait!
You again?
Are you Fier's brothers?
Yes, why?
I'm Alys.
Oh!
You're the Alys Perez.
You're really something.
You've got some nerve.
What do you want from us?
Please.
You can't let Fier leave the country.
Breathe, Alys.
Lower your pride.
You know what needs to be done.
Stay calm.
You really are something.
Are you insane?
I'm serious.
Fier can't leave the country.
Please, please!
Chance, I'm going ahead.
Maybe I might say something I’ll regret.
Please, listen to me.
You're just wasting your time, Alys.
Fier is stubborn as a rock.
What do I have to do
for you to listen to me?
What am I doing?
I feel like I'm making
a deal with the devil.
Whatever.
As long as Fier
doesn’t leave the country,
and Drake doesn’t lose
his right to their child.
Will you be willing to let go of Drake?
What?!
No!
I would do everything but that.
God knows how much I suffered
to get to this point with Drake.
Then, shut up!
My sister is already leaving,
just to give way.
Yet here you are standing in the way.
That's not my intention at all.
I'm just thinking about the child!
They will never know their father!
It's the 21st Century already, miss.
Fier's child doesn't need a father to live.
This can't happen.
I really need to do something.
Hi!
Is Drake around?
Yes, ma'am.
He's inside.
- Thanks.
- Welcome.
001131.
Unlocked.
Drake?
Drake really wants to be
a good father.
And Fier wants to take that away from him.
I need to do something.
I need to stop Fier from leaving.
She can't leave.
Pick up, please.
Damn it, Fier!
Can't you just for once—
Try to cooperate.
You’re not the only one
being affected by this.
Fier, please.
Please.
Hello, Alys?
Hello, Cristine?
Oh my god! Are you okay?
Wait, no. Where are you?
I'm coming to you.
Stay put. Stay put.
No, how's Fier?
I wanna know how Fier is.
Alys...
Come on, Cristine, please.
Please help me.
Please help Drake.
As much as I want to,
I just can't, Alys.
It's her life.
And she's really hurt too.
But what about Drake?
I don't know, Alys.
Cristine, he's your best friend.
I mean I care about Drake like you.
And I talked to Fier. I swear.
But she's made up her mind.
You know, she was really hurt
that Drake chose to let her go
despite the fact that
she's having their child.
It was too much for her.
I'm sorry.
My sister is leaving,
just to give way.
Yet here you are standing in the way.
It's the 21st Century already, miss.
Fier's child doesn't
need a father to live.
It's her life.
And she's really hurt too.
As much as I want to,
I just can't, Alys.
I'm gonna fix this, Drake.
I’ll fix this.
Ma’am, the mechanic is
already fixing your car.
But you might not be
able to use it just yet.
He says there’s a
mechanical engine problem.
He'll have to bring it to the garage.
If you'd like, I could have the
company service take you home.
Or I can book you a ride.
No, it's fine. Thank you.
It's a good thing you're still here.
At least you weren't on the road.
Something worse could have happened.
Yeah, I know.
Thank you for your assistance, okay?
Okay, Ma'am. Thank you.
Oh, by the way...
Drake still hasn’t arrived?
Not yet, Ma'am.
Update me when he’s here.
Okay?
Of course, Ma'am.
Thank you.
Another thing!
Could you please make sure he
doesn’t work on an empty stomach?
That man is already stressed enough.
Okay, Ma'am.
He does have a bit of a temper lately.
No matter what,
don't let him work without eating first.
Tell him it's an order from Ms. Alys.
Oh no, Ma'am.
He might get mad at me instead.
But,
I'll let him know.
Thank you.
That man is just way too
stubborn for his own good.
But thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Drake still hasn’t arrived.
Not even a text.
Drake, where are you?
I'm in your office.
Make sure you eat and stay safe, okay?
Are you busy?
Drake, please reply.
Zy?
Tripp?
What—
Are you okay?
Tripp...
You okay?
What happened?
One second.
I just need to submit something.
Sit down first.
Wait.
I'll be quick.
Hello.
Kindly hand this over
to the Accounting Department.
What's wrong, Zy?
What happened?
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Come with me.
Let’s go, I’ve got you.
You can cry now.
Zy...
I don’t want to sound rude but...
is crying all you can do?
Sorry, but...
I just don’t like seeing
you cry every time.
Especially not over Drake.
It's not Drake's fault!
I don't care, Zy.
The point is you're crying all over again.
Zy...
Tripp!
Listen, Zy.
Remember when I said
it's normal to get hurt?
That it's normal to cry in relationships?
But, Zy...
At this point, you're just being a fool.
Come on, Tripp.
I know you love Drake.
And I know he loves you too.
But...
it’s the same thing
over and over again, Zy.
It's unhealthy.
This isn’t right anymore.
But I love him, Tripp.
I love him.
We're already married.
Zy,
a marriage...
doesn't end after saying “I do”.
Meaning, every day of your entire life,
you chose that person.
But look at what’s
happening to you every day?
You keep on crying.
Is that the life you want?
To cry every day,
because of Drake?
I'm sorry, Alys.
I didn't mean it that way, but...
I hate seeing you cry.
I just want you to be happy, Zy.
That's it.
I know.
Bestie,
Tripp has a point.
He just hates seeing you sad.
With Drake, it’s always one
problem after another.
You know,
I am Dralys all the way.
But if you're not happy
with Drake anymore,
you should start thinking about things.
You can always run away.
And you know that.
But,
how can true happiness be measured?
Can it be measured by the
number of times that you smile?
The laughter that you share?
What's the true measure of happiness?
Hang on.
That's deep.
I know in my heart that
I'm happy with Drake.
The memories that I cherish
the most are the ones with him.
Every smile,
every time he held my hand.
I can’t bring myself to forget it.
So even though he hurt
me so badly back then,
it was just way too hard
for me to forget him.
But when does too much become too much?
Okay?
That's enough.
I'm always here.
What the hell?!
What the fuck?!
What's your problem?
Nothing, I’m sorry.
I’m confused too, Zy. I’m sorry.
It’s just that...
No matter how many times you hurt me,
I still choose you.
I’m sorry.
The only thing I want
is to get on my knees,
and beg for you to come back.
Please come back to me, Zy.
I don't know.
After all these years, Zy.
I just want to know...
Did you ever feel, even once,
how much I loved you?
I love you so much.
Even when I know you love Drake.
Five fucking years, Zy.
I gave you everything.
All genuine effort.
Even if it had to be in secret.
Even if there’s someone
else to share you with.
Even when forced, Zy.
I gave you everything.
You know what?
Even if I look like an idiot
for everything I’ve been doing.
I was at my happiest.
I was happy with that.
Zy.
After all these years,
I know I shouldn’t be saying this,
but I don't even know if I deserve it, Zy.
But please!
Just hurt me! Please!
Please...
Please, Zy! Just do anything!
Please hurt me!
I can’t.
I'm sorry.
I don't know anymore, Zy.
Break my heart, please do anything!
Hurt me. Make me feel numb.
That's the only thing I need, Zy,
for me to finally move on!
Because I don't know anymore!
I'm sorry.
I don't know anymore, Zy.
Tell me you never loved me!
Zy!
Tell me that you made a fool out of me!
That's what I need, Zy!
So, please!
But when does too much become too much?
I don't know, Bestie.
All I know is,
I feel like I lost a part
of myself when I lost him.
Because he was a part of who I was.
And honestly if I was given a chance,
I would still like him to be
a part of who I would be.
I know you understand, Bestie.
That's why you're entertaining Kent again.
My goodness.
Why are we talking about me now?
With Drake, everything just seems hopeful.
Ever since I met him.
I always look forward
to tomorrow because
I know that it will all be worth it.
Don't worry, Bestie.
Everything will be alright.
I hope so.
I hope so, Bestie.
Because I'm having such
a hard time with everything.
I feel like anytime I'll just
explode.
I feel like everything
will like crash and burn.
Bestie,
I know you're having such a hard time.
I see how much you're
fighting even if it's hard.
But remember, Bestie.
You don't have to do
this all on your own.
I'm here.
I'm always here for you.
Thank you, Bestie.
I'm tired, Bestie.
Bestie,
It's okay to be tired.
It's okay to cry.
It doesn't mean you're weak.
All it means is
you're human.
You can get hurt,
or get tired.
I know you, Bestie.
You're a strong woman.
You've been through so much.
And I know,
you'll get through this.
Thank you, Bestie.
Love you, Bestie.
Crazy & Ugly!
Crazy Aya!
Ugly Alys!
Why did I even wake up?
Here I go again.
I have to face this complicated
reality with Drake.
And then there's Tripp too.
I haven't heard from you since yesterday.
Are you really not going
to reach out today either?
What's taking you so long?
Drake, I know you're
going through a lot.
But please don't spiral.
Drake!
Yes?
How—
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
Let's have lunch together.
Good thing he still remembers me.
I thought he’d always be down.
Alright.
I'll come see you later.
I'll come get you instead.
No, it's fine. I can go to you.
Okay.
Drake?
I love you so much.
Always and forever.
To the moon and back.
I love you too, my wife.
Breakfast delivery!
With no delivery charge.
Just a smile,
and you're all set.
Good morning, Bee.
You're early.
Bee, you're forgetting to eat again.
That's bad.
One, two, three, four...
And how are you so sure
I haven't had breakfast?
Do you have psychic powers now?
Your mom said so.
For you!
Steamed bun,
and...
All I know is,
I feel like I lost a part
of myself when I lost him.
Because he was a part of who I was.
There it is!
Bee needs to eat.
Kent...
Bee?
Thank you for your efforts.
But what if,
we don't get back together?
I'd be sad.
But I'd understand.
I won't force it if you don't want me.
Like they say,
it's better to be loved
when you’re chosen,
not when you’re forced to it.
Come on, eat up.
Even if you forget about me.
Even if you don’t choose me.
As long as you choose
to take care of yourself.
Okay?
Bee.
Bee?
Did you call me “Bee”?
Why are you leaving?
Did I ever say
that I wasn't choosing you?
that I wanted to forget about you?
Bee, hold on.
What are you saying?
Are we back together?
Yes! Bee!
Bee...
Can I hug you?
Bee, I missed you so much, Bee!
I have one condition, though.
What is it?
I don't want you to be super clingy.
Just a little bit.
Alright, Bee.
I promise.
Alys, it's just a normal day.
You're not running away
from the problem.
You just want a break.
Mommy?
Dear?
Yes, Mommy?
What is it?
Tripp came by the house earlier.
Huh?
And I told him you're
gonna be in the condo so
he may be coming.
Alys?
You know, I love you so much.
And I'm always behind you in
every decision that you make.
But please put yourself first.
Okay?
Just because you love someone
it doesn't give you the license to
hurt yourself over and over again.
Okay?
Because if that's the case,
that's not love anymore.
It's just a responsibility.
And remember that love is bliss,
and not ignorance.
Okay?
Thanks, Mom.
Love you, Baby!
Always remember that.
Of course, Mom.
I love you, too.
Bye.
Mom, I know you meant well.
But I'd rather be ignorant with Drake
than to be smart and alone.
Zy...
What are you doing here?
Well...
Can we talk?
I thought I was supposed
to stay away from you?
Zy...
Tripp, please.
You asked me to stay away, right?
Then cooperate with me.
Zy,
this is the last one.
I just
really wanted to see you
for one last time.
After this...
I'm leaving.
He's leaving?
Why does it hurt?
I know I have to stay away.
But why does he have to leave?
Why?
Where are you going?
I can't say.
Somewhere far.
Wherever there's
no Alys Zyril Perez.
I just want to start over.
I want to find someone
who will love me.
For real.
I want to know how it feels
to be chosen.
Tripp, I'm so sorry.
You don't have to be.
I’m the one who fell in love with you.
Hello?
Alys, Fier is leaving!
My conscience can't
take not telling you.
What?
Where is Fier going?
She said she’s going abroad.
She's going somewhere
far away with their baby.
But that's unfair!
Alys, hurry, please!
Go to her now.
Her flight is tonight.
Her flight is tonight?!
Hey.
What happened?
I need to go.
I have to stop Fier before she leaves.
Let's go.
I’ll help you with your problem.
Before I leave.
For one last time.
Zy? What's wrong?
I'm not sure I can do this, Tripp.
You have to be strong.
Don't you want to fix things?
When are you going to face them?
But —
No, Zy. You can do this!
I believe you can do this.
Don't worry, okay?
After this,
I'll be gone, too.
But before that happens,
I want you to promise me one thing.
Never feel ashamed
to cry in front of Drake.
You know why?
When someone truly loves you,
they'll understand you.
Whether you’re crying or laughing.
As for Drake?
He loves you so much.
Okay?
Thank you for understanding me, Tripp.
Everything will be alright, okay?
For you.
For me.
For everyone.
Go.
You can do this.
I'll be here, okay?
You've got this, Zy.
Just chill, okay?
-Cris—
-Relax.
Stop following me!
I'm leaving even if you
cry or beg on your knees.
Fier, don't do this to me.
Your chance is over, Drake.
I'm done with you.
Sure.
At some point,
I may have thought I fell for you.
But you hurt me.
And when people hurt me,
I'm done.
Game over.
Sorry but that's how I roll.
Where are you going, Fier?
Would you please tell me?
You have no right to know, okay?
Don't act like a responsible father.
Fier, please.
Fier!
Please!
You've made your choice.
You chose Alys.
Fier, please!
- Fier!
- You don't have business with me,
or my child.
Please, Fier!
Fier!
Why, Drake?
Why are you doing this to yourself?
Stop begging.
I know.
I understand you and Alys.
You love each other.
Fier.
So don't worry, okay?
I'll take good care of our child.
I'll make sure she has a good life.
Please...
Don't take my child away from me.
I can't stay.
Don't take our child away from me, Fier.
I'd just hurt myself every day.
Please, Fier.
Don't do this to me, please.
Fier.
Don't keep my child from me.
I'll fix this, Fier.
Help me.
Fier.
Sorry, but I have to say goodbye.
- Fier.
- I’m sorry. No.
Fier!
Fier.
Hey!
Zy?
What happened?
- Tripp!
- Tell me.
- What happened?
Give me the keys!
You can't drive like this—
I said, give me the fucking keys!
Zy!
Tripp, please I want to be alone!
You shouldn’t drive like this—
I said I want to be alone!
Is that so hard to understand, Tripp?
Just leave me alone.
Alright.
Fine, then drive.
I’m just here.
Zy.
Slow down.
Please!
Zy, please.
You're going over the speed limit!
I don't care!
Zy, please!
Steady!
You're losing control! Please!
Zy!
Please, listen to me!
If you have a problem,
we can talk about it, please!
Just stop the car Zy, please!
Tripp...
Oh my god.
No, please!
Tripp!
Tripp, wake up. Please!
Help!
Hop on.
By the way, Zy, I'm taking you home.
Okay!
I’m still waiting for the woman
who makes my heart race.
You love Alys, right?
So much.
Relax,
I'm just trying to make you laugh.
Tripp, thank you.
I hope you’ll always be by my side.
You never leave me.
Not yet.
I still can’t.
What?
Nothing.
Zy, I love you so much.
Tripp.
Tripp?
Alys was with Tripp when it happened.
Tripp.
Alys, I’m here. I won’t leave you.
Drake, where is Tripp?
I'm just happy that Alys is alive.
Even though—
Hey, Bestie!
You need to eat, Alys.
Where's Tripp? I want to see him.
Come on, Alys.
I want to see Tripp!
Are you deaf or what?